amersc.com 2013-05-21

# American Safety Council | Privacy Policy

We recognize the importance of protecting your personal information and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This website does not collect personally identifying information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. We also take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information.

When we do collect personal information, we use this to help us better serve your needs, such as through the provision of services or information that may be of interest to you. While this information may be made available within our network of affiliated organizations as we provide services to you, we do not sell or rent your name or personal information to any third party. We do not sell or rent our mailing lists.

Our privacy policy covers this website's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the website and when you use our services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, zip code, email address, phone number, social security number, birth date, credit card information, financial information, and other sensitive information necessary to provide the associated services. If, however, we are required by law to comply with a valid legal requirement such as law, federal regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order, we may be required to release personal information. 

< Home

» Go Back to Previous Page
